Don't worry
What you have left of riba
What you have left of sin
Of kidnapping
Of banditry
Of yahoo yahoo
Of stealing government money
to make money
Of stealing and killing to
end political
offices
All of these things they are
They are small things
They have small time
Small things of small times
They are despicable
Easily they will become
disconnected from you
They don't last
And curbing over a short time
They will go away
You left them
The arm ring
For something
Something that is war
There is no doubt inside it
And it does not stop
It does not have an end
So if you leave riba my dear
brother
If you leave a transaction
that is
haram
My dear brother
If you avoid and stay away
from
banditry
From kidnapping
From stealing government
money
If you keep away from all of
these things
You have iman and yaqeen
About the day of qiyam
About the promises of Allah
About the contents of the
Quran
sunnah
About the promises